<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="head">Beatles Anthology Vol. 1</string>
    <string name="article">The album was a large success throughout the world.
        It was the first Beatles album to enter the Billboard 200 album chart
        at number one. It sold 855,473 copies in its first week, the 27th largest
        one-week sales in the Soundscan history, succeeding Fresh Horses by Garth
        Brooks. In its second week, Anthology 1 sold 453,000 copies and maintained the top spot.
        www.rockument.com
        <br></br><br></br>
        This was repeated the following week, with 435,000 copies sold.
        In its fourth week, the same quantity was sold, but the album fell to number two,
        behind Mariah Careys Daydream. In the following week, the album fell to number three
        but with 601,000 sales. Anthology 1 was certified 3× Platinum by the RIAA after six weeks
        in the US market. In all, the album spent 29 weeks on the Billboard 200, reaching
        cumulative sales of 3,639,000 scans as of April 2001. In the UK, reaction was similar,
        but the album peaked at number two, behind Robson and Jeromes eponymous album.
        In Australia, the album spent two weeks at number one in December 1995.
        <br></br><br></br>
        The cover of Anthology 1 is the first third of the Anthology collage made by Klaus
        Voormann and Alfons Kiefer. Various photographs and album covers are torn and
        collected together. Pete Bests face was torn away from the Savage Young Beatles
        record jacket in the centre of the album cover, revealing the face of his successor,
        Ringo Starr, below. The bottom leftmost photograph on the Anthology 1 cover does
        feature an unobscured Best.The missing portion of the photo was subsequently used
        on the cover of Bests 2008 album Haymans Green, an act described by one fan as
        "Pete Bests revenge".</string>
</resources>